Two ways to add a new news message.
The first is to go to dashboard,
and here in your news block,
click Add.
The second is to go to the news
listing on the front end
and click Add News message.
This example
I'm going to use a news message
in from a Google document.
So I'm going to copy it.
And then if I paste it in here
I'm going to get a bunch of Google
Doc formatting.
And I don't want that.
So I am going to go to text edit.
You can use notepad if you're on a PC.
Make sure you are in.
Plain text mode.
I want to paste it in there.
I'm going to copy it out again.
And now this time when I copy it,
it's all the formatting is gone.
So I'm
going to paste it into the body here.
And now I need to reformat this.
I'm going to delete this welcome sentence.
We want our writing on the web
to be very,
you know, straightforward and very quick.
We need to have a title for this.
And a summary.
And we need to get our
links back.
And now here we have the tags.
Now, this is completely optional, but
what you can do is you can tag your news
posts, with,
the kind of the categories
that it would fit in.
You can tag it with, you know, things
that are mentioned in the news post.
And that way people can easily
find related
related content
content related to your news post.
So this is about, let's say,
create a new one because this is about
2025 to 2026
school year.
We can have multiple tabs
or multiple tags.
All we have to do
is put a comma between them.
And this is also about forms.
So if people are looking for,
you know, news posts about forms,
they can easily find them.
Also, if we want to
we can leave this unpublished.
Let's say, you know, I got halfway through
working on this and I got pulled away.
Or, you know,
the content is still in flux.
I can leave it unpublished.
Click save.
And now when I go to my dashboard,
I can see it's still there.
But as you saw.
It's not showing to the public.
When I'm ready to publish it.
I can go back and edit
it, publish and save.
Now when we view this, we can see.
Here are the tags. So we click on farms.
All we see here
is obviously our one news item.
But if there were more tagged with farms
we would see all of them.
Your new news message is also going to be
posted to the app,
and it has its own URL here,
so you can copy and paste this into a
social media post.